<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Puzzle_For_Fun</string>

    <string name="test_1">
        <item>Which of the four is least like the other three? </item>
    </string>

    <string name="test_2">

        <item>Which country has the highest number of the cell phone user...?  </item>
    </string>

    <string name="test_3">
        <item>Which of the following is least similar to the others...?  </item>
    </string>

    <string name="test_4">
        <item>Marys father has 5 doughters Nana, Nene, Nini and Nono. Who is the 5th doughter...?   </item>
    </string>
    <string name="test_5">

    <item>What color is the square...?  </item>
</string>

    <string name="test_6">

    <item>Which of the following can be arranged into a 5-letter English word...?  </item>
</string>

    <string name="test_7">

    <item>Find the answer that best completes the analogy...?  </item>
</string>

    <string name="socrates">
        <item>Rearrange the letters of the name SOCRATES to give two other eight letter words. What will be the first letter of both words?</item>
    </string>

    <string name="findword">
        <item>6121135 is to flame as 21215120 is to ?</item>
    </string>

    <string name="forest">
        <item>Forest is to tree as tree is to ?</item>
    </string>

    <string name="percentage">
        <item>What is 40% of 190?</item>
    </string>

    <string name="numberseries">
        <item>Which number is logically follows this series: 4-6-9-6-14-6- ....</item>
    </string>

    <string name="cifaipc">
        <item>If you rearrange the letters "CIFAIPC" you would have the name of a(n):</item>
    </string>

    <string name="economy">
        <item>Who among the following is the founder of World Economic Forum?</item>
    </string>


    <string name="film_1">

    <item>What are John Abraham and Akshay Kumar professions in Garam Masala...?  </item>
</string>

    <string name="film_2">

    <item>First Programme telecast on Doordarshan is...? </item>
</string>

    <string name="film_3">

    <item>Aishwarya Rai was crowned Miss World in which year?  </item>
</string>

    <string name="film_4">

    <item>The title track of Chameli Ki Shaadi was sung by...?  </item>
</string>

    <string name="film_5">

    <item>The name of Saif Ali Khan daughter is...?  </item>
</string>

    <string name="film_6">

    <item>What is Sanjay Kapoor wife name?  </item>
</string>

    <string name="film_7">

    <item>The first film Alisha Chinai sang for was...?  </item>
</string>

    <string name="film8">

        <item>For which comedy did Tom Hanks receive his first Oscar nomination?</item>
    </string>

    <string name="film9">
        <item>What is the only film based on a TV series to get a Best Picture nomination?</item>
    </string>

    <string name="film10">
        <item>Oscar-winner Marisa Tomei’s My Cousin Vinny character was an “expert” witness in what area?</item>
    </string>

    <string name="film11">
        <item>Which Best Picture winner features the line, “I coulda been a contender”?</item>
    </string>

    <string name="film12">
        <item>Who attended the 1956 Academy Awards less than a month before becoming a princess?</item>
    </string>

    <string name="film13">
        <item>David Niven described the 1974 Oscar streaker as a man who was doing what?</item>
    </string>

    <string name="film14">
        <item>For which film did nine-year-old Justin Henry receive an Oscar nomination?</item>
    </string>


</resources>
